{
    "id": "2bf4da6040564fb0aeb00d1941bebd6f",
    "title": "State Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………… this flavor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "am liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13f1ad1719ce4644a1660acf477753da"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. fine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am feeling",
                "feel",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6a28dc88f8c54b2dae7868c77f968f58"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. your dad tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc776efb9e2d4659a0d1b5f05839f39e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I called her because I ……………….. to talk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "needed",
                "was needing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7bc6b28857d473f98dfc5efdc917451"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………….. that he is innocent.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "believe",
                "am believing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "260d362bf52a4be79571a55522b9fda5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………….. his motives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doubt",
                "am doubting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "640f5df04cd542d78d9eb3183353f7e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. what you mean.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f9afe35035b46db9ace7e9bea072fbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………… her immediately.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "recognized",
                "was recognizing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03fc3cbb00f24a73b7ae00016f76785f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meat ………………. bad.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smells",
                "is smelling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab6a1bbbc17a40498d35583a4a7c3893"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. 72 kilos.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weighs",
                "is weighing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c34f89ccae443e4878e0fb672215ab5"
        }
    ]
}